

Seoul, Republic of Korea

□ (+82) 10-5577-5814 | ■ newinh90@gmail.com | # newinh.me | □ newinh | ■ newinh | □ newinh

Summary _

1+ year experience in back-end development. Experienced embedded, Android, iOS development as a beginner, recently worked on project related to collecting data in fashion AI company.

Open culture of IT industry was so impressive that I started developmenting software. As I got help and inspired, I want to be a engineer who can help. Main skills are Python, flask, MySQL now, but i'm ready to challenge other technical skills and accomplish projects.

Skills

Programming Python

Frameworks Flask, Scrapy, pandas Infrastructures AWS, Docker, MySQL

Languages Korea(native), English(Business)

Work Experience _____

Omnious. Co., Ltd. Seoul, S.Korea

BACK-END ENGINEER Nov. 2017 -

Labeling Tool

- · Maintained back-end of in-house web application having 50+ active users for collecting fashion data to train AI model.
 - Docker, CircleCI, Rancher, AWS(EC2, S3, RDS)
- · Designed RESTful HTTP API, developed server serving them. Documented API specification for communication.
 - flask, NGINX, uWSGI, Swagger
- Established relation of domain model, designed database schema.
 - MySQL
- Built HTTP access logging system and pipeline to store it.
 - fluntd, fluent-bit
- Introduced unit testing, style guide of codebase.
 - flake8, pytest

Data Extraction & Transformation

- Extracted collected data to train AI model and pre-processed in a form that is easy to train.
- · Automated process from data extraction to data processing, developed CLI tool to access automated data transfer system.
- pandas, Celery

Crawler

- · Implemented 20+ web crawlers for collecting fashion images, developed a scheduling tool for management.
- Built serverless pipeline that stores crawled data in a storage.
- Scrapy, ScrapingHub, Zappa, AWS(SNS, SQS, Labmda)

LayGen Inc. Gyeonggi-do, S.Korea

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

· Participated to manufactoring operating module for a prototype of 3D printer and developed software control the module.

- Developed GUI so that hardware engineer can test controling each part of 3D printer.
- Python, PyQT, Rasberry Pi, Arduino

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

Gyeonggi-do, S.Korea, S.Korea

Apr. 2017 - May. 2017

Aug. 2017 - Sep. 2017

• Prototyped iOS application "Targeted Video" emphasizing object user want in video.

- Used technique of contour extraction, image segmentation and stabilization.
- Implemented video editing function that cuts or pastes object user selected.
- Swift, OpenCV

LINE Corp.

UXEnterprise Seoul, S.Korea

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

Aug. 2016 - Sep. 2016

- Prototyped Android application viewing Female biorhythm.
- Implemented connection with a measuring device using Bluetooth.
- Java, Android

Education

BoostCamp, Connect Foundation education program

Seoul, S.Korea

iOS Course

Jan. 2017 - Feb. 2017

- Developed iOS Application, "Color to Sound, Sound to Color! ChromaTone"
 - https://github.com/newinh/ChromaTone

Konkuk University

Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN ELECTRONICS

Mar. 2009 - Feb. 2016

• Graduation piece, "IOT Door Lock using Wireless Home Router & Android Device"